var data_questions = [
  {"ID":1,"Question":"A 'Pick' is called before the thrower is in the act of throwing, but the thrower does not hear it and makes a pass to a receiver, who drops it. The disc goes back to the thrower, unless both teams agree that the Pick, or Pick call, did not affect the play.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.29,"Rule":"(16.3)"},
  {"ID":2,"Question":"A 'Pick' is called while the disc is in the air and the receiver drops it. If the receiver believes the 'Pick' call affected the play, then the disc goes back to the thrower.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.52,"Rule":"(16.2.4.1)"},
  {"ID":3,"Question":"A defender can purposefully bobble the disc to themselves in order to move in any direction.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.14,"Rule":"(18.2.5.6)"},
  {"ID":4,"Question":"A defender from Team B dives, catches the disc, then immediately collides with a stationary receiver from Team A. The receiver from Team A can call a foul, but even if it is uncontested, the block will stand and the defender from Team B will have possession.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.42,"Rule":"(17.2)"},
  {"ID":5,"Question":"A defender initiates a stoppage incorrectly while the disc is in the air, and the opposition drops the disc. The disc must be returned to the thrower.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.31,"Rule":"(15.9)"},
  {"ID":6,"Question":"A defender intercepts a pass and then they initiate non-incidental contact with a receiver. It is still possible that this is a receiving foul, and if so, the interception will not count.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.29,"Rule":"(17.2)"},
  {"ID":7,"Question":"A defender is guarding an offensive player when they are within five meters of that offensive player and are reacting to that offensive player.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.22,"Rule":"(Definitions)"},
  {"ID":8,"Question":"A defender is guarding an offensive player when they are within three meters of that offensive player and are reacting to that offensive player.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.09,"Rule":"(Definitions)"},
  {"ID":9,"Question":"A defensive receiving foul is called as two players attempt to catch the disc. The call is contested and the disc is returned to the thrower to restart play. All players must return to where they were when play stopped","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.63,"Rule":"(10.2.2.1)"},
  {"ID":10,"Question":"A defensive receiving foul is called as two players attempt to catch the disc. The call is contested and the disc is returned to the thrower to restart play. All players must return to where they were when the thrower released the disc.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.17,"Rule":"(10.2.2.1)"},
  {"ID":11,"Question":"A large group of players are trying to catch a pass, and a receiver catches it. Straight after they catch it, their teammate accidentally grabs the disc from them. That is a 'hand-over' turnover.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.37,"Rule":"(13.2.3)"},
  {"ID":12,"Question":"A marking infraction may be called by any opposing player.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.16,"Rule":"(15.5)"},
  {"ID":13,"Question":"A marking infraction may only be called by the thrower.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.11,"Rule":"(15.5)"},
  {"ID":14,"Question":"A pass from team A is intercepted in the central zone by a player from team B who then intentionally drops the disc. The player from team B must re-establish possession.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.26,"Rule":"(13.6)"},
  {"ID":15,"Question":"A pass from team A is intercepted in the central zone by a player from team B who then intentionally drops the disc. This is a 'double turnover' and Team A can now take possession.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.27,"Rule":"(13.6)"},
  {"ID":16,"Question":"A pick can be called if a defender is prevented from moving towards the disc to try and get a block, regardless of where their opponent is","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.32,"Rule":"(18.3.1)"},
  {"ID":17,"Question":"A pick can occur when a defender is obstructed by another player, and this prevents them from moving towards/with the opponent they are guarding.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.07,"Rule":"(18.3.1)"},
  {"ID":18,"Question":"A pick can occur when a defender is prevented from moving towards/with their opponent, but only if they are obstructed by another opponent.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.36,"Rule":"(18.3.1)"},
  {"ID":19,"Question":"A pick can occur when any player is prevented from moving towards/with their opponent by another player.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.6,"Rule":"(18.3.1)"},
  {"ID":20,"Question":"A player 'catches' the disc by demonstrating sustained control of a non-spinning disc.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.06,"Rule":"(12.1)"},
  {"ID":21,"Question":"A player bumps into a team mate after taking a catch, and subsequently loses possession of the disc. The disc then hits the ground. This is a turnover.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.12,"Rule":"(12.2)"},
  {"ID":22,"Question":"A player catches a pass near the sideline, and then momentum takes them out of bounds. The marker may start the stall count if they are within 3 metres of the correct pivot point.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.22,"Rule":"(9.3.2)"},
  {"ID":23,"Question":"A player catches the disc and lands in the central zone, but their momentum carries them into their attacking end zone. They must establish a pivot at the nearest point on the goal line and tap the disc to the ground.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.53,"Rule":"(14.2)"},
  {"ID":24,"Question":"A player catches the disc and lands in the central zone, but their momentum carries them into their attacking end zone. They must establish a pivot at the nearest point on the goal line.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.16,"Rule":"(14.2)"},
  {"ID":25,"Question":"A player catches the disc and lands in the central zone, but their momentum carries them into their attacking end zone. They must establish a pivot at the point where they crossed the goal line.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.6,"Rule":"(14.2)"},
  {"ID":26,"Question":"A player catches the disc, and then they are injured. The injury causes them to drop the disc. That player retains possession of the disc.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.12,"Rule":"(19.1.5)"},
  {"ID":27,"Question":"A player from team A drops a catch in the central zone, and the disc stays at the location of the dropped catch. A player from team B can move to pick up the disc, and then walk away, as long as another player from team B has also been moving towards the disc at walking pace or faster, and the disc is put into play within 10 seconds of the disc coming to rest.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.25,"Rule":"(8.5.1, 8.5.2)"},
  {"ID":28,"Question":"A player from team A drops a catch in the central zone, and the disc stays at the location of the dropped catch. A player from Team B can stand over the disc and wait the full 10 seconds from when the disc comes to rest, before they put the disc into play.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.41,"Rule":"(8.5.2)"},
  {"ID":29,"Question":"A player from team A drops a catch in the central zone, and the disc stays at the location of the dropped catch. Team B must move at walking pace or faster to retrieve the disc, but there is no time limit.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.23,"Rule":"(8.5.2)"},
  {"ID":30,"Question":"A player from team A drops a catch in the central zone, and the disc stays at the location of the dropped catch. The player who takes possession from team B must establish a pivot point at any point that they can reach the disc from.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.28,"Rule":"(13.7.1, 13.9)"},
  {"ID":31,"Question":"A player from team A drops a catch in the central zone, and the disc stays at the location of the dropped catch. The player who takes possession from team B must establish a pivot point at the location of the disc.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.08,"Rule":"(13.7.1, 13.9)"},
  {"ID":32,"Question":"A player from team A drops a catch in the end zone, and the disc stays at the location of the dropped catch. Team B must put the disc into play within 10 seconds of the disc coming to rest.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.3,"Rule":"(8.5.2.2)"},
  {"ID":33,"Question":"A player gets fouled and then calls injury as a result of the foul. They must choose either to be substituted, or to charge their own team with a Time-Out.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.4,"Rule":"(19.1.4)"},
  {"ID":34,"Question":"A player initiates a stoppage incorrectly while the disc is in the air, and the opposition catches the disc. The disc must be returned to the thrower.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.24,"Rule":"(15.9)"},
  {"ID":35,"Question":"A player initiates a stoppage incorrectly while the disc is in the air, and the opposition catches the disc. The pass stands.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.15,"Rule":"(15.9)"},
  {"ID":36,"Question":"A player is making a play at the disc. They slow down and move to prevent an opponent from getting around them and also making a play at the disc. This is allowed as long as they do not initiate contact with the opponent.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.25,"Rule":"(12.7)"},
  {"ID":37,"Question":"A player is making a play on the disc. They slow down and move to prevent an opponent from getting around them and also making a play on the disc. This is a violation.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.36,"Rule":"(12.7)"},
  {"ID":38,"Question":"A player lays out for a pass and gets injured, without any contact from an opponent, then calls injury. They must choose either to be substituted, or to charge their own team with a Time-Out.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.13,"Rule":"(19.1.3)"},
  {"ID":39,"Question":"A player makes a bid and causes an uncontested receiving foul. During the bid they hurt their knee and they call injury. They must choose either to be substituted, or to charge their own team with a Time-Out.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.23,"Rule":"(19.1.3)"},
  {"ID":40,"Question":"A receiver catches a pass that is very close to the ground and there is a stoppage to discuss what happened. After discussion it is unclear if the disc touched the ground before the catch. The disc is returned to the thrower","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.13,"Rule":"(1.12)"},
  {"ID":41,"Question":"A receiver catches a pass very close to the end zone, and a few seconds later calls 'goal'. Then there is a discussion which determines it was not a goal. Players must return to where they were when the disc was caught.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.18,"Rule":"(14.1, 10.2.1)"},
  {"ID":42,"Question":"A receiver catches a pass very close to the end zone, and a few seconds later calls 'goal'. There is then a discussion which determines the receiver was in the central zone when they caught the pass, not the end zone. The players must return to where they were when the receiver said 'goal'.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.62,"Rule":"(14.1, 10.2.1)"},
  {"ID":43,"Question":"A receiver is walking to the goal line after an uncontested defensive receiving foul in the attacking endzone. The defender must wait until a pivot is established at the goal line before they can start the stall count.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.16,"Rule":"(17.2.2, 9.3.1)"},
  {"ID":44,"Question":"A rolling disc may only be stopped by the offence","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.19,"Rule":"(8.4)"},
  {"ID":45,"Question":"A stall out is called, and the thrower still has the disc. The thrower can contest the stall out if they did not have a reasonable chance to call a fast count.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.23,"Rule":"(13.4)"},
  {"ID":46,"Question":"A stoppage has occurred. The thrower has possession but the disc is not within reach of a defender. To restart play the defender nearest to the disc must call 'Disc In'.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.33,"Rule":"(10.5.1.2)"},
  {"ID":47,"Question":"A travel infraction may be called by any opposing player.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.13,"Rule":"(15.5)"},
  {"ID":48,"Question":"A travel infraction may only be called by the marker.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.17,"Rule":"(15.5)"},
  {"ID":49,"Question":"A turnover is considered a violation.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.07,"Rule":"(Definitions)"},
  {"ID":50,"Question":"A violation is called downfield, but the thrower does not hear the call and makes a pass a few seconds later. If the disc is returned to the thrower, players must return to the location they were in when the pass was thrown.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.64,"Rule":"(10.2.2.1)"},
  {"ID":51,"Question":"Actions such as intentional fouling, cheating, dangerous plays, disrespectful conversations, and other ‘win at all costs’ behaviour must be avoided","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.04,"Rule":"(1.6)"},
  {"ID":52,"Question":"After a 'stall-out' turnover play must stop.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.28,"Rule":"(13.2)"},
  {"ID":53,"Question":"After a second contested stall out due to a fast count, the stall count must restart on Stalling 6.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.24,"Rule":"(9.5.3)"},
  {"ID":54,"Question":"After a second contested stall out due to a fast count, the stall count must restart on Stalling 8.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.28,"Rule":"(9.5.3)"},
  {"ID":55,"Question":"After a stall-out turnover, the marker at the time of the stall-out must take possession of the disc.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.17,"Rule":"(13.5)"},
  {"ID":56,"Question":"After a time-out the defence can swap the player who is marking the thrower. If they do so, the stall count must restart at Stalling 1.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.18,"Rule":"(20.4.6, 9.4)"},
  {"ID":57,"Question":"After a time-out the defence can swap the player who is marking the thrower. If they do so, the stall count stays the same.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.2,"Rule":"(20.4.6, 9.4)"},
  {"ID":58,"Question":"After a turnover in the endzone, the thrower can call a time-out as they walk the disc up to the goal line.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.39,"Rule":"(20.4)"},
  {"ID":59,"Question":"After a turnover out-of-bounds the thrower incorrectly establishes a pivot on the side of the end zone, instead of at the goal line. The marker calls travel, after a pass has been made. The thrower and marker can both move to the goal line before the disc is checked in.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.55,"Rule":"(18.2.7)"},
  {"ID":60,"Question":"After a turnover out-of-bounds the thrower must establish a pivot at the correct spot before they can call a time-out.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.64,"Rule":"(20.4)"},
  {"ID":61,"Question":"After a turnover, the team that has gained possession of the disc may wait until their team mates are ready before picking up the disc","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.25,"Rule":"(8.5.1)"},
  {"ID":62,"Question":"After an uncontested 'stall-out', play continues without a stoppage.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.42,"Rule":"(13.2)"},
  {"ID":63,"Question":"After an uncontested foul by the defence the stall count restarts at a maximum of six (6).","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.25,"Rule":"(9.5.1)"},
  {"ID":64,"Question":"After an uncontested foul by the offence where the disc is returned to the thrower, the stall count restarts at a maximum of nine (9).","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.26,"Rule":"(9.5.2)"},
  {"ID":65,"Question":"After signalling readiness, and prior to the pull, the offence must stand stationary anywhere in the endzone.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.27,"Rule":"(7.3)"},
  {"ID":66,"Question":"After signalling readiness, and prior to the pull, the offence must stand with one foot on the goal line.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.12,"Rule":"(7.3)"},
  {"ID":67,"Question":"After the pull an offensive player must move at walking pace or faster to directly retrieve the disc and establish a pivot.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.09,"Rule":"(8.5)"},
  {"ID":68,"Question":"All defensive players may be at most 5 metres outside of their defending end zone when the pull is released","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.09,"Rule":"(7.4)"},
  {"ID":69,"Question":"An injury stoppage is considered to have been called at the time of the injury, unless the injured player chooses to continue play before the stoppage is called.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.1,"Rule":"(19.1.6)"},
  {"ID":70,"Question":"An injury stoppage occurs, and the injured player is leaving the field. Players are allowed to move to establish a stack before the substitute comes on the field.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.12,"Rule":"(10.2.3)"},
  {"ID":71,"Question":"An offensive player catches the disc and lands in-bounds, but their momentum causes them to leave the central zone and go out-of-bounds. They must establish a pivot in-bounds at the point where they crossed the perimeter line, and restart play with a ground tap.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.54,"Rule":"(11.3.2.1)"},
  {"ID":72,"Question":"An offensive player catches the disc and lands in-bounds, but their momentum causes them to leave the central zone and go out-of-bounds. They must establish a pivot in-bounds at the point where they crossed the perimeter line.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.12,"Rule":"(11.3.2.1)"},
  {"ID":73,"Question":"An offensive player catches the disc and lands in-bounds, but their momentum causes them to leave the central zone and go out-of-bounds. This is a turnover.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.09,"Rule":"(11.3.2.1)"},
  {"ID":74,"Question":"An offensive player catches the disc in the air and lands simultaneously with one foot in the end zone they are attacking and the other on the goal line. This is a goal.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.23,"Rule":"(14.1)"},
  {"ID":75,"Question":"An offensive player catches the disc in the end zone they are attacking but then loses possession due to ground contact related to the catch. This is a goal.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.13,"Rule":"(12.2)"},
  {"ID":76,"Question":"An offensive player catches the disc in the end zone they are attacking but then loses possession due to ground contact related to the catch. This is a turnover.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.11,"Rule":"(12.2)"},
  {"ID":77,"Question":"An offensive player catches the disc in the end zone they are attacking but then throws an incomplete pass. This is a goal.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.25,"Rule":"(14.1)"},
  {"ID":78,"Question":"An offensive player catches the disc in the end zone they are attacking but then throws an incomplete pass. This is a turnover.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.28,"Rule":"(14.1)"},
  {"ID":79,"Question":"An offensive player catches the disc in-bounds, but their momentum causes them to leave the central zone and go out-of-bounds. They must establish a pivot in-bounds at the nearest point on the perimeter line.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.57,"Rule":"(11.3.2.1)"},
  {"ID":80,"Question":"An offensive player catches the pull out of bounds. They can still choose to call 'Brick'.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.2,"Rule":"(7.9)"},
  {"ID":81,"Question":"An offensive receiver runs into a defender and knocks them over, while the thrower still has the disc. The defender calls a foul. This must be treated as an indirect foul.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.17,"Rule":"(17.9.1)"},
  {"ID":82,"Question":"An offensive throwing foul is called by the marker and the thrower still has possession. The thrower contests the foul. The thrower retains possession and any stall count must resume at maximum six.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.2,"Rule":"(9.5.4)"},
  {"ID":83,"Question":"An offside violation must be called before the receiving team touches the disc.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.1,"Rule":"(7.5)"},
  {"ID":84,"Question":"An opponent has called a foul against your team-mate and the two players are discussing the call. You are playing the point and had a good view of the play. You saw evidence that your team-mate did commit a foul. If your team-mate decides to contest the foul it is good spirit to tell them you think it was a foul","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.06,"Rule":"(1.5.1)"},
  {"ID":85,"Question":"An uncontested offensive throwing foul is called by the marker and the thrower still has possession. The thrower retains possession and any stall count must resume at maximum six.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.31,"Rule":"(9.5.2)"},
  {"ID":86,"Question":"Any offensive player may take possession of the disc after a turnover, the only exception is after an 'interception' turnover.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.59,"Rule":"(13.5)"},
  {"ID":87,"Question":"Any player may briefly extend a stoppage of play to tie their shoes, but active play may not be stopped for this purpose.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.1,"Rule":"(10.3)"},
  {"ID":88,"Question":"Before the act of throwing, a defender calls pick. A pass is attempted and it is intercepted in the air by another defender. The disc must return to the thrower, even if the pick, and the pick call, did not affect the play.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.25,"Rule":"(16.3)"},
  {"ID":89,"Question":"Defensive players are always considered 'in-bounds' for purposes of making a play on the disc.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.11,"Rule":"(11.2)"},
  {"ID":90,"Question":"Even if contact was not made on purpose (ie accidental contact), it can still be considered to be a foul.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.09,"Rule":"(15.1)"},
  {"ID":91,"Question":"For a stall-out turnover, the thrower must still be in possession of the disc when the marker starts saying 'ten'.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.11,"Rule":"(13.2.2)"},
  {"ID":92,"Question":"If a contested defensive receiving foul is called and the disc is returned to the thrower, the two players involved in the call must stay where they were when the foul occurred.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.58,"Rule":"(10.2.2.1)"},
  {"ID":93,"Question":"If a defender is guarding two opponents, they can still call a pick.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.29,"Rule":"(18.3.1)"},
  {"ID":94,"Question":"If a defender other than the marker sees that the thrower has travelled, they can call 'travel'.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.11,"Rule":"(15.5)"},
  {"ID":95,"Question":"If a defender runs within 3 metres of the throwers pivot, this is a double team.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.26,"Rule":"(18.1.1.5)"},
  {"ID":96,"Question":"If a defender uses an item of equipment, such as their hat, to help block the disc this is a violation.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.1,"Rule":"(12.11)"},
  {"ID":97,"Question":"If a defender uses an item of equipment, such as their hat, to help block the disc, the block is allowed.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.07,"Rule":"(12.11)"},
  {"ID":98,"Question":"If a line between the markers hands crosses the throwers pivot foot, this is a wrapping marking infraction","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.61,"Rule":"(18.1.1.4)"},
  {"ID":99,"Question":"If a player signals 'brick', they must also pick up the disc.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.39,"Rule":"(7.12)"},
  {"ID":100,"Question":"If a receiver is deliberately lifted into the air by a teammate to help them catch the disc, this is a turnover.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.14,"Rule":"(13.2.6)"},
  {"ID":101,"Question":"If a receiver is deliberately lifted into the air by a teammate to help them catch the disc, this is a violation, and the disc is returned to the thrower.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.36,"Rule":"(13.2.6)"},
  {"ID":102,"Question":"If a receiver jumps from out-of-bounds, catches the disc in the air, then lands in-bounds, the catch stands","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.33,"Rule":"(11.3.1, 11.5)"},
  {"ID":103,"Question":"If a receiver uses an item of equipment, such as their hat, to help them catch the disc this is a violation and the disc is returned to the thrower.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.36,"Rule":"(13.2.7)"},
  {"ID":104,"Question":"If a receiver uses an item of equipment, such as their hat, to help them catch the disc, this is a turnover.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.13,"Rule":"(13.2.7)"},
  {"ID":105,"Question":"If a turnover location is in the offence’s defending end zone, the intended thrower, before picking up the disc, may signal the goal line option by fully extending one arm above their head.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.22,"Rule":"(13.11.2.1)"},
  {"ID":106,"Question":"If after discussion players cannot agree what would most likely have occurred in a play the disc must be returned to the last non-disputed thrower.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.05,"Rule":"(1.12)"},
  {"ID":107,"Question":"If an offensive player is standing over the disc after a turnover, the marker can start the stall count straight away.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.36,"Rule":"(8.5.4)"},
  {"ID":108,"Question":"If both players initiate non-incidental contact as they attempt to catch a pass, this is not a foul on either player and the result of the play should stand.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.47,"Rule":"(17.10.2)"},
  {"ID":109,"Question":"If contact was not made on purpose (ie accidental contact) then this is the same as incidental contact","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.44,"Rule":"(Definitions)"},
  {"ID":110,"Question":"If offensive and defensive players catch the disc simultaneously, the disc is returned to the thrower.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.14,"Rule":"(12.5)"},
  {"ID":111,"Question":"If play has stopped because of a foul call, any player can choose to move to avoid a potential pick,even without agreement from the opposition.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.21,"Rule":"(18.3.3.1)"},
  {"ID":112,"Question":"If play has stopped because of a foul call, two opponents in the stack can agree to move slightly to avoid a potential pick.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.2,"Rule":"(18.3.3.1)"},
  {"ID":113,"Question":"If play is obstructed by non-players within three (3) metres of the perimeter line, a violation may be called by the thrower in possession or any obstructed player","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.11,"Rule":"(2.7)"},
  {"ID":114,"Question":"If players agree to ask a person on the sideline for their perspective on an out of bounds call, they must accept that person’s call","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.22,"Rule":"(1.11)"},
  {"ID":115,"Question":"If the disc is on the ground after a stoppage, to restart play the offence player nearest to the disc must call 'Disc In'.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.4,"Rule":"(10.5.2)"},
  {"ID":116,"Question":"If the marker is illegally positioned, and there is non-incidental contact between the thrower and the marker, this is a foul by the marker.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.13,"Rule":"(17.4.1.1)"},
  {"ID":117,"Question":"If the marker realises that the thrower has established the pivot at the incorrect spot, they can wait until they make a pass before calling travel.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.14,"Rule":"(15.8)"},
  {"ID":118,"Question":"If the marker touches the thrower in any way, the thrower may call 'Contact'.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.68,"Rule":"(15.1, 17.4.1.3)"},
  {"ID":119,"Question":"If the offence are walking the disc up from the back of the endzone they must not change speed","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.22,"Rule":"(8.5.1)"},
  {"ID":120,"Question":"If the offence are walking the disc up from the back of the endzone, they can choose to change from walking to running.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.15,"Rule":"(8.5.1)"},
  {"ID":121,"Question":"If the offence drops the pull, it is a turnover","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.04,"Rule":"(13.1.4)"},
  {"ID":122,"Question":"If the pull lands out-of-bounds without first touching the playing field, the offence can choose to call 'Brick' or 'Middle'","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.51,"Rule":"(7.12)"},
  {"ID":123,"Question":"If the pull lands out-of-bounds without first touching the playing field, the thrower in possession of the disc can wait until they get to the perimeter line before choosing to call a 'Brick'","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.32,"Rule":"(7.12)"},
  {"ID":124,"Question":"If the same marker has been straddling the thrower every time the thrower has the disc, the thrower can call a marking violation and stop play.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.13,"Rule":"(18.1.5.4)"},
  {"ID":125,"Question":"If the thrower and the marker (who is legally positioned) are both vying for the same unoccupied position, and contact occurs, it is an off-setting foul.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.51,"Rule":"(17.4.1.2)"},
  {"ID":126,"Question":"If the thrower calls 'Contact' and it is uncontested, play does not stop and the marker must resume the stall count at one (1), but only if another marking infraction has occurred during the same throwers possession","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.37,"Rule":"(17.4.1.3)"},
  {"ID":127,"Question":"If the thrower calls 'Contact' and it is uncontested, play does not stop and the marker must resume the stall count at one (1).","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.2,"Rule":"(17.4.1.3)"},
  {"ID":128,"Question":"If the thrower calls a marking violation during the act of throwing, for repeated fast counts, and the pass is incomplete, the turnover stands.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.2,"Rule":"(18.1.6)"},
  {"ID":129,"Question":"If the thrower calls a marking violation for repeated double teams, and then attempts a pass that is incomplete, the disc comes back to the thrower.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.2,"Rule":"(18.1.6)"},
  {"ID":130,"Question":"If the thrower calls a time-out during play when their team has no more time-outs, the marker must add two (2) seconds to the stall count.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.15,"Rule":"(20.5)"},
  {"ID":131,"Question":"If the thrower calls a time-out during play when their team has no more time-outs, the time-out call has no effect.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.27,"Rule":"(20.5)"},
  {"ID":132,"Question":"If the thrower calls a time-out during play when their team has no more time-outs, this is automatically a turnover.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.16,"Rule":"(20.5)"},
  {"ID":133,"Question":"If the thrower calls straddle, but the marker does not believe it is a straddle, the marker does not have to reduce the stall count and can just continue stalling.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.19,"Rule":"(15.10)"},
  {"ID":134,"Question":"If the thrower is called for a travel infraction, their teammate can contest the call.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.19,"Rule":"(15.10)"},
  {"ID":135,"Question":"If the thrower releases the disc and then taps it to a teammate before anyone else touches it, this is a turnover.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.63,"Rule":"(13.2.5)"},
  {"ID":136,"Question":"If you ignored minor travels at the start of the game, it is acceptable to call them once the scores are close and the game is about to end.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.13,"Rule":"(1.3.7)"},
  {"ID":137,"Question":"If you no longer believe that a call you made was correct, you should retract it","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.06,"Rule":"(15.11)"},
  {"ID":138,"Question":"If you no longer believe that a call you made will benefit your team, you can retract it.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.48,"Rule":"(15.11)"},
  {"ID":139,"Question":"If, in attempting to stop a rolling disc, a player significantly alters the disc’s position, they must immediately move it to the correct spot.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.49,"Rule":"(8.4.1)"},
  {"ID":140,"Question":"In games without timekeepers, teams must get ready for the pull without unreasonable delay","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.06,"Rule":"(7.1.1)"},
  {"ID":141,"Question":"Incidental contact is contact that does not affect the play and is not dangerous in nature.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.21,"Rule":"(Definitions)"},
  {"ID":142,"Question":"Incidental contact is specifically defined as 'contact that does not affect continued play'.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.49,"Rule":"(Definitions)"},
  {"ID":143,"Question":"It is acceptable to make calls in retaliation to an opponent’s call","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.15,"Rule":"(1.6.5)"},
  {"ID":144,"Question":"It is solely up to the defence to take reasonable efforts to avoid the occurrence of picks.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.16,"Rule":"(18.3.3)"},
  {"ID":145,"Question":"It is solely up to the offence to take reasonable efforts to avoid the occurrence of picks.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.2,"Rule":"(18.3.3)"},
  {"ID":146,"Question":"It promotes Spirit of the Game to compliment an opponent when they make a good play on the disc.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.04,"Rule":"(1.5.3)"},
  {"ID":147,"Question":"'Making a play for the disc' is a valid excuse for initiating contact with other players.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.1,"Rule":"(12.8)"},
  {"ID":148,"Question":"Non incidental contact that occurs as a receiver and a defender move towards a single point simultaneously should be treated as offsetting fouls.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.18,"Rule":"(17.10.2)"},
  {"ID":149,"Question":"People on the side line must not give advice on foul calls, unless they are asked by the players involved","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.1,"Rule":"(1.10)"},
  {"ID":150,"Question":"Teams must get ready for the pull within 10 seconds of the opposition signalling readiness.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.32,"Rule":"(7.1.1)"},
  {"ID":151,"Question":"The defence are double teaming the thrower. The thrower makes a pass that hits one of the defenders, and results in a turnover. The disc must come back to the thrower.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.16,"Rule":"(18.1.6)"},
  {"ID":152,"Question":"The disc is in the air when an injury stoppage is called, and play continues until the disc hits the ground. If the injury is not the result of a foul, the turnover stands, and play restarts there after the stoppage.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.13,"Rule":"(19.1.7)"},
  {"ID":153,"Question":"The goal lines are part of the central zone.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.13,"Rule":"(2.4)"},
  {"ID":154,"Question":"The interval between the start of each number in the stall count must be at least one (1) second.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.04,"Rule":"(9.1)"},
  {"ID":155,"Question":"The marker calls 'Travel' as the thrower makes a pass, and the receiver drops it. If the receiver believes the 'Travel' call affected the play, then the disc goes back to the thrower.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.29,"Rule":"(18.2.8)"},
  {"ID":156,"Question":"The marker can have their head above the throwers pivot, as long as it is one disc diameter away from the torso of the thrower.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.46,"Rule":"(18.1.1.4)"},
  {"ID":157,"Question":"The marker must leave a gap of one second between the start of the word ‘Stalling’ and the start of the word ‘One’ in a stall count.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.36,"Rule":"(9.1)"},
  {"ID":158,"Question":"The perimeter lines are part of the playing field","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.14,"Rule":"(2.3)"},
  {"ID":159,"Question":"The place where a disc becomes out-of-bounds and where a disc went out-of-bounds is always the same.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.32,"Rule":"(11.5, 11.7)"},
  {"ID":160,"Question":"The pull has hit the ground and is rolling along the ground. The thrower fumbles the disc as they go to pick it up and it hits the ground. The thrower can pick the disc up again, as long as they never establish sustained contact with, and control of, the disc","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.24,"Rule":""},
  {"ID":161,"Question":"The pull is the throw from one team to the other that starts play at the beginning of a half or after a goal, and it is not considered a legal pass.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.12,"Rule":"(Definitions)"},
  {"ID":162,"Question":"The pull lands in bounds and stops in the end zone, without ever going out-of-bounds. The thrower can choose to establish a pivot at the location of the disc or at the goal line closest to where the disc stopped","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.24,"Rule":"(7.10)"},
  {"ID":163,"Question":"The puller can have one foot in the central zone when the pull is released, as long as the other foot is in the end zone.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.2,"Rule":"(7.4)"},
  {"ID":164,"Question":"The thrower calls ‘Fast count’. The marker does not contest, and immediately resumes the stall count with the number last fully uttered before the call, minus one. During the same stall count the thrower calls ‘Straddle’ and again the marker does not contest. The marker must stop straddling, and resume the stall count at 1.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.39,"Rule":"(18.1.3)"},
  {"ID":165,"Question":"The thrower calls ‘Fast count’. The marker does not contest, and immediately resumes the stall count with the number last fully uttered before the call, minus one. During the same stall count the thrower calls ‘Straddle’ and again the marker does not contest. The marker must stop straddling, and resume the stall count with the number last fully uttered before the call, minus one.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.24,"Rule":"(18.1.3)"},
  {"ID":166,"Question":"The thrower calls a marking violation during the act of throwing, for repeated marking infractions. The pass is incomplete. The disc must come back to the thrower.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.38,"Rule":"(18.1.6)"},
  {"ID":167,"Question":"The thrower establishes a pivot at the wrong spot and a travel is called. The thrower still has the disc. Play does not stop but the thrower must establish the pivot at the correct spot. The thrower must wait until the marker says 'Stalling' before they can make a pass.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.46,"Rule":"(18.2.6.2)"},
  {"ID":168,"Question":"The thrower from Team A releases the disc, then taps it to avoid an interception by Team B. The disc hits the ground. The result of the play stands and Team B gets possession.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.1,"Rule":"(13.2.5)"},
  {"ID":169,"Question":"The thrower is allowed to intentionally deflect a pass off an opponent, as long as they move from the spot they threw it before they catch it.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.2,"Rule":"(13.2.4)"},
  {"ID":170,"Question":"The thrower releases the disc, then taps it to avoid an interception by a defender. The disc hits the ground. The defender gets possession where they would have caught the pass.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.4,"Rule":"(13.2.5)"},
  {"ID":171,"Question":"The throwing motion is the motion that transfers momentum from the thrower to the disc in the direction of flight and results in a throw. Pivots and wind-ups are not part of the act of throwing.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.26,"Rule":"(Definitions)"},
  {"ID":172,"Question":"The throwing motion is the motion that transfers momentum from the thrower to the disc in the direction of flight and results in a throw. Pivots and wind-ups are part of the act of throwing.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.43,"Rule":"(Definitions)"},
  {"ID":173,"Question":"The time at which a goal is scored is when the defence accepts a goal has occurred.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.25,"Rule":"(14.3)"},
  {"ID":174,"Question":"The time at which a goal is scored is when the disc is caught and the player in possession is in contact with the end zone.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.06,"Rule":"(14.3)"},
  {"ID":175,"Question":"There is a turnover and the disc has landed out-of-bounds. The thrower, who is standing where the pivot is to be established, can immediately restart play if a non-player gives them the disc.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.25,"Rule":"(11.8)"},
  {"ID":176,"Question":"There is an uncontested defensive receiving foul in the attacking end zone. The receiver and their defender must move to the goal line before the check.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.54,"Rule":"(17.2.2)"},
  {"ID":177,"Question":"There is an uncontested defensive receiving foul in the attacking end zone. The receiver gets possession in the end zone, then the disc is checked in, and then the receiver moves to the goal line.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.39,"Rule":"(17.2.2)"},
  {"ID":178,"Question":"There is an uncontested foul called by the thrower during the act of throwing, and then the intended receiver drops the disc. The disc must go back to the thrower, even if the foul did not affect the play.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.37,"Rule":"(16.3)"},
  {"ID":179,"Question":"To restart play when the thrower has the disc and there is a defender within reach, the defender must touch the disc and say 'Disc In'.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.59,"Rule":"(10.5.1)"},
  {"ID":180,"Question":"To restart play when the thrower has the disc and there is a defender within reach, the defender must touch the disc.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.16,"Rule":"(10.5.1)"},
  {"ID":181,"Question":"Unless you have caught the disc while in the air and have yet to land, you must maintain contact with the playing field when you make a pass.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.19,"Rule":"(18.2.1.1, 18.2.2.1)"},
  {"ID":182,"Question":"Whenever a foul or violation call is made, play stops immediately and no turn over is possible. There are no exceptions to this rule.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.28,"Rule":"(16.1)"},
  {"ID":183,"Question":"You are allowed to intentionally foul the thrower to prevent a goal, as long as you do not contest the call","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.08,"Rule":"(1.6.2)"},
  {"ID":184,"Question":"You can call dangerous play regardless of whether or when, contact occurs.","Answer":1,"Difficulty":0.11,"Rule":"(17.1.1)"},
  {"ID":185,"Question":"You can only call dangerous play if contact occurs.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.15,"Rule":"(17.1.1)"},
  {"ID":186,"Question":"You can throw while running after catching a pass, and while in the air, as long as you release the disc before your third ground contact.","Answer":0,"Difficulty":0.34,"Rule":"(18.2.2.1)"}
];